

# **PROFILE**

I am a full stack developer from Fort Mill South Carolina. I develop websites using frameworks such as vue and react. I have experience working as a solo contractor for a local and as a member of a team of a nation wide staffing company. I am graduating from BYUI in April 2024 with a BS in Software Engineering and a certificate in Web Development. In my free time I enjoy mountain unicycling with my friends, and Camping in Lynnville NC. Feel free to check out my website below where you can learn more and view my full portfolio.

# CONTACT

PHONE: 8035042034

EMAIL:

skylerjsimpson@gmail.com

WEBSITE:

skylersimpson.netlify.app



# SKYLER SIMPSON

Full Stack Web Developer

# **EDUCATION**

Brigham Young University Idaho 2020-2024

BS, Software Engineering, Certified in Web Development GPA 3.2

### **SCHOOL EXPERIANCE**

### 24 hour Hackathon Event Oct 2023

- Created A coding Language Website for Children in 24 hours with my team.
- This Website used basic language and provided tutorials for kids to learn how to program with text rather than block coding.

# Web Services Final Project April 2023

- Developed a web version of the popular game code names and its expansion codenames Duet.
- The project is hosted using Netlify and Mongo DB to maintain the web page and the Database, the routes can all be seen using swagger.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Stone Crest Suites: Web Full Stack Developer Aug 2023–Jan 2024

- Developed a full stack webpage that allowed users to reserve office space
- Implemented director privileges, allowing directors to add office space and edit office amenities.
- Used Netlify, Render, and MongoDB as my hosting services.

OnDiem Dental Staffing: Front End Developer Jan 2024-PRESENT

- Contributed to the creation of OnDiems staffing website through sprint plannings and ticket completions.
- Used Vue to create new components and update existing components.
- Gained experience working on a larger development team and working for a company.

# **SKILLS**

HTML	CSS	JavaScript	Vue
Node	Sequelize	React '	TailWind
Python	Django	C++	Excel
ORMs	Figma	GitHub	